{
    "subject": "resource/Slint",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Math_rock",
    "human_readable": "Slint's genre is Math rock.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9761066436767578,
            "question": "Is Slint considered part of the Math rock genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5831841826438904,
            "question": "What genre of music is Slint known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47090914845466614,
            "question": "What is a defining characteristic of Math rock music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.434644877910614,
            "question": "Slint's music is often described as being in what musical style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36987224221229553,
            "question": "Name a musical style that Slint's music is associated with."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34049057960510254,
            "question": "Give an example of a genre that incorporates complex mathematical elements into its music."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30946582555770874,
            "question": "What kind of music does Slint play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2724713683128357,
            "question": "What musical subgenre is characterized by complex time signatures and mathematical structures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2680952847003937,
            "question": "To what musical category does Slint belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12675067782402039,
            "question": "Which genre often features intricate rhythms and unconventional song structures?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Slint's genre is Math rock.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7487_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what musical category does Slint belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7487_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical subgenre is characterized by complex time signatures and mathematical structures?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7487_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does Slint play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7487_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7487_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Slint is associated with the math rock genre. In particular, file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7487/re-ranker-msmarco/41.txt mentions \"Math rock\" as a style of music developed in the late 1980s and early 1990s, characterized by complex rhythmic structures, counterpoint, odd time signatures, angular melodies, and extended chords. Additionally, file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7487/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt lists Slint as one of the bands associated with the math rock genre."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Slint's genre is Math rock.\" Specifically, Document 41 describes math rock as a style of music characterized by complex, atypical rhythmic structures and mentions Slint as one of the bands associated with this genre."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}